<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>project | H. Sherry Zhang</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>project</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/headshot.png</url>
      <title>project</title>
      <link>/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quickdraw</title>
      <link>/project/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/2020/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/huizezhang-sherry/quickdraw&#34;&gt;quickdraw&lt;/a&gt; package allows you to download and retrieve the dataset categories from the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/googlecreativelab/quickdraw-dataset&#34;&gt;Google quickdraw dataset&lt;/a&gt;. It has been used as the data source for the class projection of &lt;a href=&#34;https://iml-monash.netlify.app/project/project.html&#34;&gt;ETC3250 Introductory Machine Learning&lt;/a&gt; at Monash University.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judgeface</title>
      <link>/project/2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 16:58:07 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is part of human nature to react to changes by expressing emotions while in many court systems, Justices are required to remain still to ensure the judgement is not biased. In this study, I assess the facial expressions of six Justices in six cases heard in the High Court of Australia based on Paul Ekman&amp;rsquo;s Facial Action Coding System, which decomposes facial expressions into movements of facial muscles, also called action units. Command Line, Docker, R and a facial recognition software, OpenFace, are used. I found that Justices generally remain impartial during the court proceedings, however, negative emotions (i.e., sadness, fear, and anger) are detected more intensely and frequently than positive emotions (i.e., happiness and surprise), especially in criminal cases (i.e., drugs and sexual assaults).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
